dianjinwa.com 2019-08-20

# Privacy Policy - Dianjinwa Video - Free Hot Videos

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to Dianjinwa Video Privacy policy!

When you use our services, you’re trusting us with your information. We understand this is a big responsibility and work hard to protect your information and put you in control.

Your privacy is important to us. Therefore we have developed a Privacy Policy that describes the ways Dianjinwa Video collect, store, use, and manage the information, including personal information, and data that you provide or we collect in connection with our website.

Please note that the scope of this Policy is limited to information and data collected or received by Dianjinwa Video through your use of the Service. Dianjinwa Video is not responsible for the actions of third party people or companies, the content of their sites, the use of information or data you provide to them, or any products or services they may offer. Any link to those sites does not constitute our sponsorship of, or affiliation with, those people or companies.

This site USES Google cookies to provide services and analyze traffic.Your IP address, user agent, and performance and security metrics are Shared with Google to ensure service quality, generate usage statistics, and detect and resolve abuse problems.

By using the Service, you are expressing your agreement to this Policy and the processing of your information and data, including your personal information, in the manner provided in this Policy.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SERVICE.

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us with the information provided in the "Contact Us" section of this website.
